A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
The toilet paper is folded neatly into a triangle.
Absolutely perfect.
And every frame along the wall is aligned exactly with the ground.
The candles on the left have burned down to the same height as the candles on the right.
Absolutely perfect.
Balance between left and right.
Perfect symmetry.
That is what is most important in this world.
Now it's on to school.
Come on, Liz.
Patty, let's go.
Now you're suddenly in a big rush to go.
What's the point in hurrying?
We're already three hours late.
Let's go.
I mentioned it...
Can I hear brotherly power and retention,
and can I hear you again?
Thank you.
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
出会った理由は途絶びに突きつけられて
触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ確かになれる
サルの経matへどうしたらいい accompanying
体情に吐き刺させた ME
I've got it, why don't we do another dissection lab?
あ、説明ださ elesの言葉は
portsの людиが伝えすことだ
Ever since you became our teacher,
all we've done is dissect animals every day.
Oh, but you see, Maka,
today will be different.
This time our specimen is infinitely more interesting
than a mouse or frog.
Are you ready for it?
Today we'll be poking around the insides
of this little guy here.
A rare species of cuckoo, endangered, I believe.
Dissect an endangered species?
Um, Dr. Stein, I don't think we can dissect that.
It's really rare, nearly extinct, you know?
All the more reason to dissect one
before the entire species dies off.
He's seriously crazy.
He must be insane.
Tsubaki, Maka, why don't I see
Soul and Blackstar up there with you?
Are they planning to come to class?
They're probably skipping.
Again. Those two idiots are hopeless.
Sorry, Tsubaki. We're switching out.
I'm gonna be soulsmeister from now on.
Geez, if they want to be together so much,
maybe they should just be partners.
Huh? What do you think?
No, nothing never happened to you!
Never, never, never!
I guess they'll miss out on the excitement.
I'm sure that you are all aware by now.
But a very interesting new student
will be joining our class today.
It's the-
The new student.
Kid's first day at the Academy.
Will it be an entrance to remember?
Hyah!
Listen up!
There's someone who must be assassinated by the great Blackstar!
Right now, at Death Weaponmeister Academy, one rumor stands out from the rest.
They say that the son of Lord Death himself has enrolled.
Everyone's talking about the new guy instead of focusing on me.
I'll have to kill him!
Clearly, it's a good thing you've got your priorities straight.
What in the crap is that damn kid planning on getting her anyway?
I've been waiting around here for three hours!
Would you look at us now?
Raised on the streets, but here we are, students at the Academy.
We've come a long way, huh, Patty?
Yeah, it's gonna be freaky awesome!
Have you ever seen such a beautiful building?
My father's school is magnificent.
Perfectly balanced, perfectly symmetrical.
Hey, are you the new kid we've been hearing so much about?
This is my first day. Are you here to show me around?
You show up three hours late and you think I've been waiting here to give you a tour?
If you'd been here at seven like you're supposed to, you could've looked around yourself.
What's that? What did you say, seven?
No, it can't be seven! Say eight, damn it! Eight is better!
What? Huh?
It's physically impossible to cut the number seven in half and make it symmetrical!
It has to be eight instead! Eight cut in half vertically or horizontally stays perfectly symmetrical!
Take it back! I beg you, you! Just say eight, please!
Uh, dude, is there something wrong with you?
Yes, he's absolutely insane!
Yahoo!
No one's permitted to take attention away from me!
What is that? Some kind of monkey?
It doesn't matter if you think you're the sun and skin!
Yeah, it must be a monkey!
That's right! I'm going to kill you today and then tomorrow you'll have to do what's about me!
Look up there, kid! I think that thing is yelling something at you. Not sure what, though.
Left star is gone! Left star is the greatest assassin who ever lived!
How does that sound, you kid? Are you scared yet?
Face it, kid! I'm much too big of a guy for you to handle, and you know it!
Do you see how the very ground shakes beneath my feet?
Look what you did! It's not symmetrical anymore, you jerk!
Ugh, nice. Now you've really done it.
Are you ready for this? I'm going to give you a taste of my black star assassin skills!
It's not an assassination if you've been seen, idiot.
You are a disgusting pig!
Are you really so eager to risk your soul that you'll pick a fight with the Grim Reaper?
Liz, Patty, weapon forms!
Right!
We've done nothing but fights since we got off the streets. I could use a...
If you want to fight, let's do it! Come on, Sol!
You're the one who's looking for a fight, Black Star, not me.
I'll play along, but I'm warning you, new guy, if we do this, you'll lose.
Damn straight! We're gonna make one badass team together!
This guy was strong enough to bring down Anubis.
He's gotta have guts to try and outshine me all the time.
These two punks may not be perfect, but they did manage to defeat Sid and hold off Dr. Stein's attacks.
I'll need to keep my guard up.
Let's go.
Hey, what?
Dr. Stein! It's Sol and Black Star! They're fighting someone outside!
Sol, that idiot. What is it now?
Excuse me, Dr. Stein! There's a rule about two Meisters dueling on campus. It states that in order for the duel to continue, there must be a professor there to witness it.
I hate to stop here, but it can't be helped.
We'll have to postpone the dissection as Sol and Black Star's partners Maka and Tsubaki come along with me. Everyone else study something.
We can't even get close to the guy!
What was that? You're looking for a more up-close and personal fight?
Fine by me!
We'll see!
We can't even get close to the guy!
You're looking for a more up-close and personal fight?
Fine by me!
We'll see!
Let's see!
See?
No!
All right!
In those of them, let's find yourself Jokito or 단ium,
We'll see.
Dammit!
What the hell?
Oh, man, that hurt really, really bad!
Did you think a pair of normal pistols would be enough for a Grim Reaper?
We aren't like regular guns that shoot bullets.
We shoot compressed wavelengths of our Meister soul.
Dammit.
How dare he go easy on us?
Oh, my. They probably should have picked a different opponent.
Dr. Stein, is that the boy?
The one with the guns?
Is he the new kid that everyone's been talking about so much?
Yep.
That's Lord Death's son, Death the Kid.
It was his own decision to attend the Academy.
But he won't be a normal student.
His abilities are far greater than anyone else's here.
But why Blackstar?
Sorry, Tsubaki. We're switching out.
I'm gonna be Soulsmeister from now on.
Tsubaki?
Is something wrong?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
My dear soul-seeing Scythemeister Maka, can I borrow you for a moment?
Malia?
I have a special lesson in mind for you today.
Oh, okay.
Now, now. There's no reason to be worried.
It's a very simple question.
Take a look at the duel.
Watch Kid and his twin pistols as they fight.
I want you to pay particular attention to their souls' wavelengths.
Normally, it's almost impossible to sink the wavelengths of two weapons like that.
But the connection between all three of them is strong and very stable.
And the weapons seem to share a respect for them.
No, that's not the word.
Admiration. Is that it?
Exactly correct.
A good observation.
The twin pistols are called the Thompson sisters.
They grew up on the streets.
Their lives were much harder before they met Kid.
It's natural they would have a strong admiration for him.
The partnership works for Kid, too.
It's good for him to be around people so different.
The Thompson sisters' laid-back attitudes have a positive influence on him by quieting his neurotic tendencies.
They do make a really good team, those three.
Don't they?
You can't even compare them to our two idiots out there.
Let's hurry up and finish this guy off.
It's about time.
For what?
You're a twig with fear of your impending death.
When you say that, it just makes me want to laugh.
You won't be laughing when you taste our power of friendship.
That's right.
It's incredible.
The power is beyond belief.
What?
Let's do it.
Yeah.
Transform!
Whoa.
That's so cool!
I don't think they're taking this very seriously.
Come on, soul!
Let's do it!
You shot!
Why the hell did you kick me with your head, moron?
Ah!
I don't know!
Do it right this time!
You're freaking heavy!
I can't pick you up!
I'm not heavy.
Maka slings me around without breaking a sweat.
Blackstar and soul are definitely lacking in the compatible wavelength department.
So it seems.
Come on, you stupid swords!
They're just here to lift you up!
What the hell are you doing hitting me with your soul's wavelength?
That hurt, you idiot!
Oh, my bad.
It's almost hard to watch.
Those morons can't seem to sense each other's wavelengths at all.
Before a Meister and his or her weapon fight an opponent,
they need to adjust their wavelengths to each other.
Blackstar, it's over between us.
What exactly are you saying, soul?
If we try to stay together like this, I'll only end up hating you.
It's for the best.
Huh?
Hey, can I shoot them now?
Let's wait. Things are just starting to get good.
Oh, I understand.
But even though it's over, would it be okay if we stay friends?
You idiot!
Of course we're still going to be friends forever!
Oh, soul!
Blackstar!
They need professional help.
Oops.
Sorry.
My fingers slipped.
We can't just quit in the middle of a fight.
Right!
We're not giving up till we beat him!
Okay.
We'll see how well that works.
No!
Let's see how you handle a taste of my bone weights!
Blackstar's specialty is martial arts.
But kid is just playing with him.
And the way he's been fighting today, soul has no chance against him either.
You're as slow as you are stupid.
You're going down!
You idiot!
You fell for it!
Gotcha!
You're going down!
Okay!
Now I really want to kill that guy!
Our partners are pretty useless, huh?
You're going down!
Okay.
Now I really want to kill that guy!
Move that for ya!
Ha! Gotcha!
Okay, now I really want to kill that guy.
Our partners are pretty useless, huh?
And now it's time to see the power of a grim reaper.
Let's go, Soul Resonance!
Huh? It looks like their souls have begun to expand.
Now they're showing off their true strength.
Okay! Let's see what you got, huh?
Reaper Shmeeper, bring it on!
Execution mode ready. Prepare to die.
Um... I don't like the looks of that.
Come on, what are you gonna do, little man?
I've got a lot scarier than you!
So there!
Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha!
Resonance stable. Noise at 0.3%.
Black Needle's Goal Wavelength Fully Charged!
Preparing to fire. Feedback in four seconds.
Three...
One...
Two...
Three...
One...
Two...
one...
NO WAY IS SOMETHING LIKE THAT GONNA HURT, KEY!
THAT'S INCASTABLE!
BLACKSTAR!
Oh man, what were those idiots thinking?
Looks like a decisive defeat.
But, you can hardly expect anything less from the son of the Grim Reaper.
His potential is great and already far above that of any other Meister at the Academy.
And somehow I have a feeling that he still isn't showing us everything he can do.
Lord Death's very own flesh and blood?
What I wouldn't give to study that one.
Ay-yi-yi.
Great, here we go again.
What happened to him?
Not much, it's just a little cut.
What got cut?
I think I might have an idea of what it was.
Hmm?
Well, I'm pretty sure it happened during Soul's last attack on Kid.
I think that Kid got a little hair cut off from his bangs.
After the explosion happened and things died down, Kid finally noticed that one side of his bangs was shorter than the other.
His symmetry was off, so he spit up blood and fell over.
He's the one bleeding now, so that means we actually won the fight, huh?
Yeah, right!
It means we won, and I, Blackstar, have defeated the Reaper!
I knew it!
Who's gonna be talking about this guy now?
Are you really sure you're alright now, Blackstar?
Hell yeah, of course I'm alright!
I did death today, I'm awesome!
Yeah, it was amazing.
Hey.
Don't let yourself get involved in stupid fights, alright?
Come on.
That's exactly what you used to tell me, Soul.
Yeah, I guess I was the uncool one of us today, huh?
Please try not to do anything too crazy from now on.
Yeah, right!
Nothing's too crazy for me now!
I've beaten up a Reaper after all, it's crazier than that!
Tsubaki's the only one for him.
I don't think anyone else could handle Blackstar.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Coming?
Yeah.
Sorry.
Let's stay cool, okay?
You got it.
Eh!
So, I heard my son had an eventful first day at school.
Kid can be difficult sometimes.
I hope no one's hurt too badly.
I wonder, what does the soul of Lord Death look like?
I'll take a look.
Huh.
I can't see it.
All right, everyone.
I'm going to go ahead and take Kid home now.
I think he could use a little rest.
Bye!
Right!
See you later!
I don't understand.
Kid's his son and he has a soul.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Why can't I see Lord Deaths?
Hey, Maka.
What are you doing standing around like that?
Let's go back inside.
Yeah, okay.
I guess it's possible that Lord Death just doesn't have a soul.
Oh, well.
Whatever.
くず星 きらめく 夢のほしさ
I wanna be 行こうぜ 行こうぜ 行こうぜ 行こうぜ 行こうぜ 行こうぜ 行こうぜ
I am forever. I want to be my name on You
Thank you.